



Zaragoza, Spain | +34 611 00 83 48 | dkay22@gmail.com | dinaspencer.net

Education & Certifications

University of North Carolina at Wilmington B.A. in Spanish & Psychology, 2005

170 Hour TEFL Certification – International TEFL Academy – July 2017

UI Design - DesignLab - May 2018

Profile

My goal is to improve processes and leave things better than I found them. In all my roles, I provide a positive user experience through top-notch communication. 10 years of experience in various sectors.

Tools

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, WordPress, PHP, HelpScout, Zendesk, Asana, Sketch, Slack, Google Analytics, MailChimp, SurveyGizmo, Intercom, HootSuite, Visme, Canva

Languages

Spanish -C1

English – Native

Skills

People: Teaching with warmth and empathy, customer support with speed and accuracy, community management

Technology: Email marketing, web development and design, analytics, HTML and CSS

Professional Experience

2013-Present English as a Second Language Coach

Online and in-person English classes. Currently working with pharmaceutical and engineering professionals to enhance communication skills. Overwhelmingly positive feedback from learners.

2020 - Seasonal Customer Support Specialist - You Need A Budget
Navigate queue of help requests in HelpScout, open and follow
tickets on Zendesk, provide empathetic and confident support,
deep-dive into niche areas like credit cards and direct bank import.

2019-2020 Community Manager/Marketing - PharmaBoardroomArticle writing and editing for B2B digital publication with 100,000+

monthly visitors. Social media channel management with HootSuite, increasing followers by over 50%. Measure web traffic trends with Google Analytics. Send targeted email blastings in MailChimp, customizing their design with HTML & CSS. Redesign e-commerce site using JavaScript in Shopify back-end. Data visualization design with infographic tools for KPI reports. Manage media partnerships with pharma and health conferences.

2015-2018 Community Manager - Lingo Live

Deliver on KPIs related to NPS scores and satisfaction. Manage team of 50 remote independent contractors, evaluating performance metrics and supporting their goals. Collaborate with engineers to resolve platform issues via ticketing system. Design and distribute newsletters in MailChimp.

2008-2013 Project Administrator & Coordinator

Assisted on projects in education, nonprofit, advertising, and construction companies. Tracked finances and documentation in Excel, met important deadlines, conducted presentations.





Zaragoza, España | +34 611 00 83 48 | dkay22@gmail.com | dinaspencer.net

Formación y Certificaciones

Licenciatura de Humanidades (Español y Psicología): University of North Carolina at Wilmington (EEUU), 2005

TEFL: Certificado de Enseñanza de Inglés Como Lengua Extranjera (170 horas), International TEFL Academy, 2017

Diseño UI: DesignLab, mayo 2018

Perfil

Lo que me motiva es crear, diseñar, analizar, y mejorar. Mi meta profesional es crear una UX positiva a través del diseño y la comunicación. Cuento con diez años de experiencia laboral en varios sectores con altas habilidades de edición, analítica web, redacción, presentaciones, coordinación de proyectos, y atención al cliente con un carácter amable y empático.

Herramientas de Informática

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, HelpScout, Zendesk, Google Analytics, WordPress, Sketch, Asana, Trello, InVision, MailChimp, HootSuite, SurveyGizmo, Intercom, Visme

Idiomas

Español – C1

Inglés - Nativo

Habilidades

Soft skills:

Empatía y amabilidad, colaborando y apoyando equipos Comunicación eficaz y estratégica Enfoque en el cliente y sus necesidades

Hard skills:

Diseño web con HTML, CSS, JavaScript Análisis y visualización de datos

Experiencia Laboral

2013-Actual Docente de Inglés

Clases particulares presenciales y online para más de 100 alumnos con resultados positivos. Actualmente dando clases a profesionales del sector farmacéutico. Experiencia previa como auxiliar de conversación en EOI, ESO y Bachillerato.

2020 - Atención al Cliente (Temporal) - You Need A Budget

Atender peticiones de ayuda en una empresa de software estadounidense. Gestionar la cola de peticiones en HelpScout, abrir tickets en Zendesk, seguir la línea de comunicación de la empresa con un tono amable y profesional.

2019-2020 Community Manager, Editor Digital - PharmaBoardroom Edición y redacción de artículos para una publicación digital B2B con más de 100.000 visitantes mensuales. Gestionar redes sociales con HootSuite, aumentando seguidores más de 50%. Medir trends en Google Analytics. Diseñar y enviar correos de marketing en MailChimp con HTML y CSS. Mejorar diseño de la página de e-comercio con JavaScript en Shopify. Visualización de datos para informes KPI. Gestionar intercambio de publicidad con conferencias internacionales de salud.

2015-2018 Community Manager - Lingo Live

Colaborar con equipo global para contratar, apoyar, y formar 50 profesores autónomos de varios idiomas. Solucionar problemas de informática colaborando con el equipo de ingenieros. Diseñar correos con MailChimp.

2008-2015 Administradora y Coordinadora de Proyectos

Trabajar con proyectos en empresas de educación, publicidad, construcción y sin ánimo de lucro. Seguimiento de documentación y finanzas, cumplir con fechas límites, hacer presentaciones públicas.